

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.

## **EXPERIENCE**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER **▼ ACS TECHNOLOGIES**July 2017 - present , Programming and watching cute cat videos.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER-ASSOCIATE **▼ ACS TECHNOLOGIES** July 2016 - July 2017 , Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT APPRENTICE **▼ ACS TECHNOLOGIES** August 2015 - July 2016, Making coffee and baking cookies.

INTERN **▼ ACS TECHNOLOGIES** May 2015 - August 2016 ,

## **EDUCATION**

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, MINOR IN APPLIED MATHEMATICS Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

## **SKILLS**

- > JavaScript
- > Vue|S
- > C#/ASP.NET MVC
- Intercom

- jQuery
- CSS/LESS/SASS
- > Go
- > PostgreSQL

## **CONTACT**

levinerjamie@gmail.com; (843) 229-1193; , Florence; jamieleviner.com; https://github.com/jamieleviner